<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rishabh Anand</title>
    <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rishabh Anand</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 12:45:55 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Link</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/musical/link/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:51:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/musical/link/</guid>
      <description>I make music to escape. With more than 400 hours of lessons on youtube, I taught myself how to play guitar and the keyboard. I sing sometimes.
Some of my music is here :
Youtube Some of my covers are here:
Instagram </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/photo/link/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:48:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/photo/link/</guid>
      <description>I like taking photos. I take a lot of photos infact. And I post a lot. On Instagram.
Check it out. Leave a like. Drop your comments. Follow if you want to see more.
Link to instagram </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realization</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/realization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:39:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/realization/</guid>
      <description>It slowly began to dawn on me that I had been staring at her for an impossible amount of time. Lost in my thoughts, lost in the sight of her. But her face didn&amp;rsquo;t look offended or amused. It almost looked as if she were studying the lines of my face, almost as if she were waiting.
I wanted to take her hand. I wanted to brush her cheek with my fingertips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cities</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/cities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/cities/</guid>
      <description>I love cities with plenty of lights at night. I love a city where you can find a place to do nothing but stare at those lights when the night falls. Like what I am doing right now, in front of the balcony window, staring at the lights far far away, across the sea.
That&amp;rsquo;s what I love about Mumbai. That&amp;rsquo;s what I love about Delhi. Every time that I took a plane alone and land in Mumbai at night, every time that I walked on to that bridge in Delhi at night by myself, I am not afraid, I don&amp;rsquo;t feel lonely, for I could see thousands and thousands of sources of light all around me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/end/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:38:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/end/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve heard when we die we usually see a flash and then it&amp;rsquo;s all over. Like the recap of how we played out part. The choices we made to be where we were in our last moments.
Hello friend,
What do you think happens when we die ? I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about it a lot lately. What if it&amp;rsquo;s just the sad bizarre end everyone fears it is? One moment you&amp;rsquo;re with everyone you love, laughing, kissing, and the next moment it just ends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Hours</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:37:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/hours/</guid>
      <description>I light a cigarette and idly sip the water from my glass. When I am bored or nervous I tend to plow right through whatever beverage I might have on hand at the time. It is one of the reasons I can&amp;rsquo;t drink anymore. Doing this with water just cleans out my system and makes me have to piss a lot. Doing it with whiskey generally ends with my ass falling asleep in the back of a police cruiser, or an ambulance, or the neighbor&amp;rsquo;s lawn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/here/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:37:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/here/</guid>
      <description>Hello friend,
Why do you still put up with me? Why do you listen to what I say? Don&amp;rsquo;t you freak out? Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re just like me, can&amp;rsquo;t open up about it. Others do. I can see why they do it. I&amp;rsquo;m fucked up. It&amp;rsquo;s okay tho. I am used to it. Everyone has their own problems to face. And I can see what they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want another hallucinating weirdo in their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lies</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/lies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:36:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/lies/</guid>
      <description>Hello friend,
Do you lie to yourself too? Do you put yourself in illusions? I am doing that quite often. Lying about my own feelings. Maybe that&amp;rsquo;s what I need right now. An illusion. That everything is fine and I can live this way. But can I? Should I change things? Should I try to take a chance or just settle with what I have? What if I ruin everything? That would suck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Again</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:36:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/again/</guid>
      <description>Hello friend,
I&amp;rsquo;m here again. Shit. This is developing as a habit. I need to tone it down. Since I am already here. Do you feel anything? I don&amp;rsquo;t. Not anymore. Not just pain or happiness. Anything.
Fuck. How did it come to this? When did I became so isolated? I used to have friends. Now it&amp;rsquo;s just you. Or was it always an illusion? Having people around who care about you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kawai</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/kawai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:34:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/kawai/</guid>
      <description>Hello friend,
That&amp;rsquo;s lame. I think you need a name. But then again you&amp;rsquo;re just in my head. Shit. I&amp;rsquo;m actually doing this. Talking to an imaginary person. It&amp;rsquo;s not like I have a choice. I have to get it out. Everything that I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking. Everything that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out. Maybe you could help me. Don&amp;rsquo;t think this is some sorta cozy safe place for cute talks. No. This is about the reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immortal</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/immortal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:11:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/immortal/</guid>
      <description>I know that we all think we&amp;rsquo;re immortal, we&amp;rsquo;re supposed to feel that way, we&amp;rsquo;re graduating. The future is and should be bright, but, like our brief four years in high school, what makes life valuable is that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t last forever, what makes it precious is that it ends.
I know that now more than ever. And I say it today of all days to remind us that time is luck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BalckBoard Auto-Logger</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/project/balckboard-auto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 19:03:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/project/balckboard-auto/</guid>
      <description>Intro A python based application that automatically logs in into your accounts and attends your classes on cuchd.blackboard.com website. I wrote this script STRICTLY for EDUCATIONAL PURPOSES and I am NOT RESPONSIBLE for any non-disciplinary action commited by its users, i.e., all the students of Chandigarh University (yes, ALL, not just CSE or AIT !)
Usage So you&amp;rsquo;re done with the installation. But, how do you use it? It&amp;rsquo;s really simple actually, you run the same runME.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AST</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/work/ast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 19:02:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/work/ast/</guid>
      <description>AST Guardian A project I worked on while interning at Arima Labs as a Python Developer. This project works with the following :
Vehicle entry and exit detection (open-CV/open-VINO) Number plate text extraction (OCR) Video hosting/masking (Flask/ngrok) Sending live link to client (FAST2SMS) Link </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Games</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/work/games/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 19:02:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/work/games/</guid>
      <description>Various games that I built while learning python:
Basic Black Jack Chess Dice Drawing HangMan MusicalFace Snake Sudoku with a solver using BAcktracking algorithm. Tetris Wind down and relax !
Link </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PiFUxZ</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/work/pifuxz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 19:00:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/work/pifuxz/</guid>
      <description>Textured - 3D model generation using a single 2D image. I built this while I was interning over at vInnovate Technologies as a Computer Vision Expert. Exisiting projects from Facebook like PiFu is able to generate 3D models with one image and PiFuHD is able to generate textured models using multiple images. PiFuxZ is best of both worlds.
Link </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leddit</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/work/leddit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 19:00:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/work/leddit/</guid>
      <description>Reddit clone using Typescript and React
I built this when I was learning ReactJS. I usd typescript because it&amp;rsquo;s JavaScript but better. I also used other technologies like,
GraphQL URQL/Apollo Node.js PostgreSQL MikroORM/TypeORM Redis Next.js TypeGraphQL Link </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AfterShock Predictions</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/project/aftershock/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 18:55:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/project/aftershock/</guid>
      <description>AfterShock Analysis of the 2018 article &amp;lsquo;Deep learning of aftershock patterns following large earthquakes&amp;rsquo; by Phoebe M. R. DeVries, Fernanda Viégas, Martin Wattenberg &amp;amp; Brendan J. Meade, published in Nature.
Intro In a world, divided by fear, of losing your loved ones, of losing your loved belongings,of losing your life, we hope to come up with a solution that keep you and your dreams safe. Because that’s what EarthQuake’s take away&amp;hellip; Even after the major tremor, what hurts more is the AfterShocks that follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning with IoT</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/project/federated-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 18:53:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/project/federated-learning/</guid>
      <description>Federated Learning On Distributed Private Health Data On Smartphones The smartphones of the people probably carry the most valueable but also private data. Since using data promisses to be one of the best ways to fight back against COVID-19, it is highly desirable to get access.
By using a Federated Learning approach with PySyft it is possible to learn from the private data right on the smartphone, with the data never leaving the device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>xZphish</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/work/xzphish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 18:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/work/xzphish/</guid>
      <description>Phishing library written in shell. I built this while I was learning CyberSecurity through IBM.
Features Latest and updated login pages. Mask URL support Beginners friendly Multiple tunneling options Localhost Ngrok (With or without hotspot) Link </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social-Bot</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/work/instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 18:40:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/work/instagram/</guid>
      <description>All in one social media bot for people who are on social media but are too lazy to open and surf it. We usually call them INTROVERTS !
Support for Multiple sites !
Instagram Twitter Facebook Reddit StackOverFlow Youtube Link </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flappy Bird</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/work/flappy-bird/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 18:09:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/work/flappy-bird/</guid>
      <description>Flappy_Bird Game made on Tkinter and PyGame (Two versions).
The game was then automated using NEAT(Neuroevolution of Augmenting Topologies) algorithm.
Link </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/project/sentiment-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 12:45:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/project/sentiment-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This project aims to classify the emotion on a person&amp;rsquo;s face into one of seven categories, using deep convolutional neural networks. The model is trained on the FER-2013 dataset which was published on International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML). This dataset consists of 35887 grayscale, 48x48 sized face images with seven emotions - angry, disgusted, fearful, happy, neutral, sad and surprised.
Working This implementation by default detects emotions on all faces in the webcam feed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
