<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>notes on Rishabh Anand</title>
    <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/</link>
    <description>Recent content in notes on Rishabh Anand</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 12:45:55 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Realization</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/realization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:39:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/realization/</guid>
      <description>It slowly began to dawn on me that I had been staring at her for an impossible amount of time. Lost in my thoughts, lost in the sight of her. But her face didn&amp;rsquo;t look offended or amused. It almost looked as if she were studying the lines of my face, almost as if she were waiting.
I wanted to take her hand. I wanted to brush her cheek with my fingertips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cities</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/cities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/cities/</guid>
      <description>I love cities with plenty of lights at night. I love a city where you can find a place to do nothing but stare at those lights when the night falls. Like what I am doing right now, in front of the balcony window, staring at the lights far far away, across the sea.
That&amp;rsquo;s what I love about Mumbai. That&amp;rsquo;s what I love about Delhi. Every time that I took a plane alone and land in Mumbai at night, every time that I walked on to that bridge in Delhi at night by myself, I am not afraid, I don&amp;rsquo;t feel lonely, for I could see thousands and thousands of sources of light all around me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/end/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:38:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/end/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve heard when we die we usually see a flash and then it&amp;rsquo;s all over. Like the recap of how we played out part. The choices we made to be where we were in our last moments.
Hello friend,
What do you think happens when we die ? I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about it a lot lately. What if it&amp;rsquo;s just the sad bizarre end everyone fears it is? One moment you&amp;rsquo;re with everyone you love, laughing, kissing, and the next moment it just ends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Hours</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:37:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/hours/</guid>
      <description>I light a cigarette and idly sip the water from my glass. When I am bored or nervous I tend to plow right through whatever beverage I might have on hand at the time. It is one of the reasons I can&amp;rsquo;t drink anymore. Doing this with water just cleans out my system and makes me have to piss a lot. Doing it with whiskey generally ends with my ass falling asleep in the back of a police cruiser, or an ambulance, or the neighbor&amp;rsquo;s lawn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/here/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:37:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/here/</guid>
      <description>Hello friend,
Why do you still put up with me? Why do you listen to what I say? Don&amp;rsquo;t you freak out? Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re just like me, can&amp;rsquo;t open up about it. Others do. I can see why they do it. I&amp;rsquo;m fucked up. It&amp;rsquo;s okay tho. I am used to it. Everyone has their own problems to face. And I can see what they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want another hallucinating weirdo in their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lies</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/lies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:36:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/lies/</guid>
      <description>Hello friend,
Do you lie to yourself too? Do you put yourself in illusions? I am doing that quite often. Lying about my own feelings. Maybe that&amp;rsquo;s what I need right now. An illusion. That everything is fine and I can live this way. But can I? Should I change things? Should I try to take a chance or just settle with what I have? What if I ruin everything? That would suck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Again</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:36:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/again/</guid>
      <description>Hello friend,
I&amp;rsquo;m here again. Shit. This is developing as a habit. I need to tone it down. Since I am already here. Do you feel anything? I don&amp;rsquo;t. Not anymore. Not just pain or happiness. Anything.
Fuck. How did it come to this? When did I became so isolated? I used to have friends. Now it&amp;rsquo;s just you. Or was it always an illusion? Having people around who care about you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kawai</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/kawai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:34:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/kawai/</guid>
      <description>Hello friend,
That&amp;rsquo;s lame. I think you need a name. But then again you&amp;rsquo;re just in my head. Shit. I&amp;rsquo;m actually doing this. Talking to an imaginary person. It&amp;rsquo;s not like I have a choice. I have to get it out. Everything that I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking. Everything that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out. Maybe you could help me. Don&amp;rsquo;t think this is some sorta cozy safe place for cute talks. No. This is about the reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immortal</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/immortal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:11:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/immortal/</guid>
      <description>I know that we all think we&amp;rsquo;re immortal, we&amp;rsquo;re supposed to feel that way, we&amp;rsquo;re graduating. The future is and should be bright, but, like our brief four years in high school, what makes life valuable is that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t last forever, what makes it precious is that it ends.
I know that now more than ever. And I say it today of all days to remind us that time is luck.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
