<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>One Shot on Rishabh Anand</title>
    <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/one-shot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in One Shot on Rishabh Anand</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 12:45:55 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/one-shot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Realization</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/one-shot/realization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:39:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/one-shot/realization/</guid>
      <description>It slowly began to dawn on me that I had been staring at her for an impossible amount of time. Lost in my thoughts, lost in the sight of her. But her face didn&amp;rsquo;t look offended or amused. It almost looked as if she were studying the lines of my face, almost as if she were waiting.
I wanted to take her hand. I wanted to brush her cheek with my fingertips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cities</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/one-shot/cities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/one-shot/cities/</guid>
      <description>I love cities with plenty of lights at night. I love a city where you can find a place to do nothing but stare at those lights when the night falls. Like what I am doing right now, in front of the balcony window, staring at the lights far far away, across the sea.
That&amp;rsquo;s what I love about Mumbai. That&amp;rsquo;s what I love about Delhi. Every time that I took a plane alone and land in Mumbai at night, every time that I walked on to that bridge in Delhi at night by myself, I am not afraid, I don&amp;rsquo;t feel lonely, for I could see thousands and thousands of sources of light all around me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Hours</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/one-shot/hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:37:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/one-shot/hours/</guid>
      <description>I light a cigarette and idly sip the water from my glass. When I am bored or nervous I tend to plow right through whatever beverage I might have on hand at the time. It is one of the reasons I can&amp;rsquo;t drink anymore. Doing this with water just cleans out my system and makes me have to piss a lot. Doing it with whiskey generally ends with my ass falling asleep in the back of a police cruiser, or an ambulance, or the neighbor&amp;rsquo;s lawn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immortal</title>
      <link>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/one-shot/immortal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:11:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thefenrislycaon.github.io/note/one-shot/immortal/</guid>
      <description>I know that we all think we&amp;rsquo;re immortal, we&amp;rsquo;re supposed to feel that way, we&amp;rsquo;re graduating. The future is and should be bright, but, like our brief four years in high school, what makes life valuable is that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t last forever, what makes it precious is that it ends.
I know that now more than ever. And I say it today of all days to remind us that time is luck.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
